前情提要
英国被不明外国势力袭击了
The UK's under attack by a suspected foreign power.
你知道政府的反应是什么吗 我都不知道
Do you know what the government's response is? Neither do I.
格雷戈里·诺克斯 重案组弗林探长
Gregory Knox? DS Flynn, Homicide.
我需要你跟紧我 快点 别出声
I need you to follow me, quickly and quietly.
进去
Get in.
弗林病房的所有摄像头都连在独立安全的网络上
The cameras on Flynn's ward were isolated, on a secure network,
由七楼的反恐指挥部控制
controlled from the seventh floor of CTC.
先锋行动失败
Operation Vanguard is compromised.
因为我们 纳皮尔小队的核心人员
Thanks to us, a core member of Napier's team was
有了完全没有限制的权限
given a full, unrestricted pass.
路易 这是瑞秋
Louie, Rachel.
不管背后是谁 他们一定监视着我们的一切
Whoever's behind this is watching everything we do.
我们认识的人里 谁有那么大的权限
Who do we know with that much access?
我的建议是 只要能保证我们安全 就应该使用种族定性
I'm advocating the use of racial profiling wherever it keeps us safe.
-大臣 我们得 -我完了
- Minister, we have to... - Now I'm finished.
卡迪加 就像我们说过的那样 你现在什么都不要说
Like everything else we've discussed, Khadija, you keep this under wraps.
直到你把这作假丑闻的内幕都挖出来给我
Until you can give me everything, the deep fake scandal.
特纳先生 你为什么不回应维多利亚·贝洛
Mr Turner, why won't you respond to the love child
对于你私生子的说法
allegations made by Victoria Bello?
你还不明白吗
In case you haven't noticed,
艾萨克 你已经丢了在政府的工作 都结束了
Isaac, you've just lost your job, in government! It's over!
不
No!
欢迎来到这场「移花接木」的噩梦 艾萨克
Welcome to the nightmare that is correction, Isaac.
听我说 阿比盖尔 现在不太合适
Look, Abigail, this is a bad time.
爸妈要去城市旅行 我也没办法啊
Well, I can't choose when Mum and Dad go on a city break.
我有很多话要跟你说
I've got tons I need to talk to you about.
我开始玩播客了
I'm starting a podcast.
也许你明天可以给我讲讲
Maybe you can tell me about it tomorrow.
别担心 你在这我可以睡的很安稳
Don't worry, I'll sleep, now you're here.
自从家里被盗后就一直这样 太奇怪了
It's been like this since the burglary. Which is weird
因为盗窃发生的时候我不在家
because that happened in the daytime when I wasn't even home.
-什么盗窃 -我以为爸告诉你了呢
- What burglary? - I thought Dad would've told you.
家里几个月前被入室盗窃了 却没人告诉我
You were burgled months ago and nobody told me?
我可是个警探啊
I'm a police detective!
真相捕捉
第二季  第四集
热水器设置定时了
The boiler's on a timer.
如果你想冲澡 给你5分钟
If you want a shower, you've got five minutes.
下楼
乘客气囊
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
就附近
Not far.
你就是为了这个让我下来吗
That's why you said to come down?
-只是告诉我别光着身子在公寓里跑 -没错
- So you could tell me not to walk around the flat naked? - Exactly.
我光着身子的事就让你这么不爽吗 瑞秋
Does the idea of my naked body offend you, Rachel?
公寓里的私密性不够
It... It's not the most private of flats.
这话是什么意思
What does that mean?
邻居吗 他们能看到公寓里面吗
The neighbours? Can they see in?
差不多吧
Something like that.
什么 他们是变态吗
What, are they perverts?
你为什么不把他们抓起来呢
Why don't you just go and arrest them?
已经在处理了
I'm working on it.
只是猜测
Look, it's just a suspicion, OK?
但可能性非常大
But it's a pretty strong suspicion,
所以你别光着身子到处晃就行了
so just definitely don't walk around naked.
行吧 明白了 天啊
Yeah, I get it. Jesus.
你为什么不能在楼上告诉我呢
Why didn't you just tell me all this upstairs?
因为他们还会监听
Because they listen, too.
如果这样你都能习惯 瑞秋
If it's all the same to you, Rachel...
那我不会待太久了
..I don't think I'm going to stay much longer.  Actually,
实际上 我希望你能待到之前说的那个时间点
I sort of need you to stay for as long as you said you would.
如果你突然改变计划 他们会怀疑是我跟你说什么了
If you change the plan, they might assume it's because I've told you.
-然后呢 -我不想让他们发现 我知道被监视了
- And?  - And, I don't want them to know that I know that they're watching.
那又如何
And what?
难道我就该让他们监视着 待在公寓里吗
I'm supposed to hang out in the flat while they spy on me?
你会发现自己很快就习惯了
You'd be surprised how quickly you get used to it.
你他妈太奇怪了
You are fucking weird.
爸
Dad?!
还有更多呢 快看
There's more, look.
11 12 13 14 15
11, 12, 13, 14, 15
-16 17 18 -艾萨克
- 16... 17, 18...  - Isaac!
最近被解雇的安全大臣艾萨克·特纳
The recently dismissed Minister for Security, Isaac Turner,
尚未发出回应
is yet to respond to requests for comment.
贝洛女士声称她和议员的关系开始于四年前
Ms Bello claims the affair happened four years ago,
就在议员拜访尼日利亚期间
while the MP was visiting Nigeria.
现在她 还有三岁的儿子
Now she and her three-year-old son
正在申请英国绿卡
are applying for British citizenship
却受到了政治干涉
amid questions of political assistance and interference.
我以为麦肯奇不会让这个播出呢
I told McKenzie to shut this down.
你知道
You knew about it?!
我 我知道有这个传闻
I-I knew it was circling.
艾萨克·特纳有没有利用他在内政部的权力
Did Zac Turner use his power at the Home Office
来干涉这位年轻母亲的申请呢
to block this young woman's application?
你为什么没告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
没什么好说的 这就是毫无根据的抹黑
There's nothing to tell. It's a baseless smear.
你们俩上楼去
You two, upstairs.
不要看电视
And stay away from the TV.
她有手机的 艾萨克
She's got an iPhone, Isaac.
-喂 -你看到新闻了吗
- Hello?  - Have you seen it?
你当然看到了 我需要你在有人插手前
Of course you've seen it. Look, I need you to find the paperwork
找一下所有的相关文件
before anyone else gets their claws into it.
我需要一份贝洛申请的完整时间表
We need a full timeline of Bello's application
可以表明我们部门没有进行过干预
to show there was no interference from our department.
我被调到政策部了 艾萨克 我不再...
I've moved to Policy, Isaac. I don't work...
我知道你不再为我工作了 我又不傻
I know you don't work for me any more, I'm not an idiot.
我只是想 你应该愿意帮我
I-I just guessed you might be interested in helping me,
毕竟这事也牵连到你
seeing as this implicates you too.
你知道我乐意帮你
You know I'd want to help you.
但是
But?
但你现在有点像过街老鼠
You're a bit...toxic right now.
所以你还在查看我的支持率是吗
So you're still checking my numbers?
你为什么要说那些话
Why did you say those things?
听我说 我现在正在想办法 等我查清楚了
Look, I'm working on something, but when I'm done,
过街老鼠就不是我了
it won't be me who's toxic.
我尽力吧
I'll do what I can.
我不是你那些溜须拍马的同事 也不是爱丽莎
I am not one of your fawning staff, I am not Aliza,
我是你老婆
I am your wife.
这到底怎么回事
What is going on?
你会留下吗
Will you stay?
好吧
Fine.
但是 我希望今晚我们能待在一起
But I want us to spend the evening together.
一起做什么呢
What did you have in mind?
聊天 就像姐妹一样
Talk? You know, be sisters?
而且我想给你讲讲我的播客
And I want to tell you about my podcast.
今晚 好
Tonight. Sounds good.
有事吗
Can I help you?
我给你打过电话 长官
I tried calling you, ma'am.
总警司加兰德让我负责你不在时的重案组报告
DSU Garland instructed me to run the homicide reports in your absence.
所以呢
And...?
所以我想看看你能不能给我些指导
I just wondered if you had any guidance for me?
我现在休恩假呢
I'm on compassionate leave.
我知道 加兰德提过
Yes, DSU Garland mentioned that.
我只是
I just...
不想没跟你打招呼
..didn't want to tread on your toes
就踩过界
without checking.
先锋行动怎么样了
What's the status on Vanguard?
-没有变化 -监控网络呢
- No change. - The camera networks?
应该是被入侵了 技术人员正在想办法
Assumed compromised. Tech's working on a solution.
等他们想出办法来告诉我一声
Update me when they have one.
还有 交叉对比爱迪生·姚和约瑟夫·姆旺吉袭击事件中的
Meanwhile, cross-check ballistics and forensics from the hospital against
弹道学报告和法医报告
the attacks on Edison Yao and Joseph Mwangi.
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
这就够你忙的了
That should keep you busy.
说话安全吗
Is it even safe to talk?
暂时安全
For now.
我们已经扫描了硬件 没发现任何设备
We've swept the hardware, found no devices.
估计是通过网络入侵的
Assuming the compromise came via the network,
-已经断线处理了 -但是
- it's neutralised, it's offline. - But...?
我们可以开放海岸
Well, we can open the beach,
但回到水里应该不安全
but it's not safe to go back in the water.
只要行动重新上线就有风险
Soon as the ops room's back online, it's at risk.
如果他们连这都能入侵 那我们还能去哪
Where the fuck are we supposed to go if they can hack us here?
也许我没资格说这个
Look, it's maybe not be my place to ask,
老大 但...
Guv, but...
我们排查过所有内部人员了吗
are we doing enough to rule out internal compromise?
你有明确的怀疑对象吗
Anyone in particular you're concerned about?
没有 但我只是不想改变行动之后
No-one in particular. I just don't want to move the op,
发现有问题的人并没被换走
only to find out the problem's moved with us.
你说的对 汤姆 这确实不该是你操心的
You're right, Tom. It's not your place.
懂了
Understood.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?!
我不知道他们装了哪种麦克风
I don't know what kind of microphones they have out there.
我甚至不知道家里安不安全
I don't even know if the house is safe.
见鬼了 所谓的警方保护
Fuck sake! Our police protection?
不过就是监控这个地方罢了
For all we know it was them that bugged the place.
你看到有人在保护我们吗
Did you have eyes on the whole time?
保护 为什么他们要监控我们
Eyes on? Why would they want to bug us?
西蒙 这种跟安全相关的事我不能插手
It's the kind of thing I can't get into, Simmy. Security things.
我说的不是安全的事
I'm not talking about security things.
我问的是新闻上的那个女人
I'm asking about the woman on the news
她说她的孩子是你的
who said she had your child.
维多利亚 她是个护工
Yeah. Victoria. She's a care worker.
她照顾过我妈 直到去世
She looked after Mum, at the end.
所以你认识她
So, you know her?
我们在葬礼上见过
We met at the funeral.
现在呢
And now what?
她难道就瞎编个故事 只为拿到绿卡吗
She's just cooked this up to try and get into the country?
没这么简单
It's bigger than that.
背后有人指使 一开始我以为是中国人
Somebody else is behind it. At first I thought it was China,
为了抹黑我 为了拿到面部识别系统的合同
trying to smear me in the run-up to the facial rec contract.
现在呢
And now?
现在
Now...
谁关的 谁干的
Who turned that off? Who turned it off?!
艾萨克 够了
Isaac, enough!
你把电源踢掉了
You tripped the switch.
听着 对不起
Look, I'm sorry
我不该居高临下地跟你说话
for all the "need to know" crap.
我需要你相信我
I just need you to trust me.
这是什么
What's all this?
以贝洛女士的名义 我们今早给特纳先生出了律师函
On behalf of Ms Bello, we have written to Mr Turner this morning,
要求他进行DNA亲子鉴定
requesting a sample of his DNA for paternity testing.
如果特纳先生在7天之内不提供DNA样本
If Mr Turner fails to provide a sample within seven days,
我们就会提起诉讼
then we will begin court proceedings.
贝洛女士声称她和议员的关系开始于四年前
Ms Bello claims the affair happened four years ago,
就在议员拜访尼日利亚期间
while the MP was visiting Nigeria.
现在她 还有三岁的儿子
Now she and her three-year-old son...
不 不 这不是中国人搞出来的
No, no, this isn't about China.
也不是面部识别公司的事
It's not about facial rec.
这是针对我个人的
This is about me.
有人想毁了我
Someone's trying to destroy me.
艾萨克·特纳深陷移民丑闻的漩涡之中
Isaac Turner has found himself at the centre of an immigration scandal.
问题是
The question still remains...
看见了吗
This ring any bells?
你不是说这事可以掩盖吗
I thought you said you could shut this story down.
-BBC那边我递过话了 -这不是BBC
- I stopped the BBC from breaking it. - It's not on the BBC!
麦肯奇 现在的消息发布通道可多了去了
It's all different channels these days, McKenzie!
我之前还对他寄望颇高呢
Had such high hopes for him, you know.
-从抹黑他的人那里吗 -我别无选择
- From the person who sacked him? - I didn't have much of a choice.
反正他也没有机会东山再起了
It's hardly going to help his chances of bouncing back.
长官 哈特指挥官想见您
Sir? Commander Hart to see you.
-又来事了 没完没了 -内政大臣
- And more shit, hot off the shovel. - Home Secretary.
丹尼 看过这个了吗
Danny. Seen this?
我是来给您做先锋行动的简报的
It's your daily briefing on Vanguard, sir.
去吧 麦肯奇 出去
Go on, McKenzie. Fuck off.
昨晚的袭击之后
Following last night's attack,
整个行动受到了极大的影响
the operation remains profoundly compromised.
通话和视频监控系统都不安全了
Comms and camera networks are not secure.
技术人员正在加班加点的修补 但在那之前
Technical staff are working round the clock to safeguard the op, but until then...
简直就是在1956年 是谁干的
It's 1956. Who's doing this?
我们的目标范围很广
Our focus is widening.
除了中国之外 还有其他嫌疑人
Suspects besides China are being explored.
我也这么想的 太典型了
I thought as much. Just typical.
什么
I'm sorry?
有可能啊
It may have been possible.
谁知道北京那边在想什么
Who knows what Beijing is thinking?
我就是觉得不对头
It just didn't sound right to me.
我没听懂 内政大臣
You've lost me, Home Secretary.
中国没必要逼迫我们搞定面部识别合同
China didn't need to strong-arm us into the facial rec contract.
他们早就志在必得
They had it in the bag.
既然你已经决定了 为什么还要特纳大臣进行报告呢
But why commission Turner's report if your mind was already made up?
公众需要看到流程 丹尼
The public need to see a process, Danny.
所以声音都需要被听到
All voices aired.
特纳的担心有道理
And Turner's concerns are valid.
选中国确实有风险
China poses a security risk.
是 我们知道
Yes. We know.
那你也该知道
Then you should also know
跟不跟中国合作
that the risk posed by going with China
所带来的风险都是同等的
is the same as the risk posed by not going with China.
他们要是想黑我们 这都算是对我们开恩了
If they feel like hacking us, that is in their gift.
那你会怎么选
So, who would you go with?
除中国之外 后面还有谁呢
After China, who else is there?
内政大臣所说的一切都证实了瑞秋·凯里的推论
Everything the Home Secretary says backs up Rachel Carey's theory.
中国不会赢得面部识别的竞标
China's going to lose the facial rec bid,
美国在后面排着队呢
the US are waiting in line.
你还是不相信她吗
You still don't trust her?
孰是孰非尚且没有定论
The jury is very much out on that.
你觉得她当时情绪稳定吗
Did she seem stable to you?
你是说 在她发现弗林警探被杀之后吗
You mean, after she found DS Flynn murdered?
弗兰克有说什么吗
What's Frank got to say for himself?
到目前为止 他都神出鬼没的
So far, he's proving elusive.
我们需要安全的监控以及通讯设备
We need a clean shot and secure comms.
如果弗兰克不是罪魁祸首 他就能帮忙
If Frank's not to blame, he can bloody well help.
如有必要 亲自给他捎句话
Doorstep him if you have to.
提醒他特殊关系是互惠的
Remind him the special relationship is meant to be reciprocal.
那是什么
What was that?
往回倒 往回倒
Take it back. Take it back.
恐怕倒不了
I'm afraid I can't take it back.
我们正在做手术
We are midway through a procedure.
你看到那个肿块了吧
You saw that lump, didn't you?
你要记住 这些检查只是预防措施
You have to remember, these tests are a precaution
因为你的活检和CT报告还没有出来
while we await the reports from your biopsy and CT.
如果报告还找不出症结
If the results are still unclear
就得做胶囊内窥镜检查
we will move on to capsule endoscopy.
我之前做过不是吗
I had one of those, didn't I?
没有 胶囊内窥镜检查是说
No. With capsule endoscopy,
你会吞下一个装有无线摄像头的小药丸
you'll swallow a small pill containing a wireless camera,
药丸会通过小肠
which passes through the small intestine,
拍摄和传输数百张视频图像
taking and transmitting many hundreds of video images
用于分析
for analysis.
现在用摄像头能做到的事情真是了不起
It's remarkable the things that can be done with a camera nowadays.
是么
Is that so?
■
吉玛
孔氏餐厅？
先是罗文不接我电话 现在里斯也不接了
First Rowan's not answering my calls, now Rhys.
我才不当大臣 也就十分钟吧 就被遗弃了么
I stop being a minister for what, ten minutes, I'm a pariah?
要是我还在内政部
If I was still at the Home Office,
我会让公关狂喷这帮混蛋
I'd have the PR war machine gunning for these pricks.
可你不是在内政部
Well, you're not at the Home Office.
你在家
You're at home.
我能提个建议吗
Can I make a suggestion?
同意亲子鉴定吧
Just agree to the paternity test.
你还不明白吗 不会真去做亲子鉴定的
Don't you see? There won't be a paternity test.
因为他们会伪造证据
Because they'll fake it,
就跟伪造其他东西一样
like they fake everything else.
你好
Hello?
你家有后门吗
Does your property have rear access?
非常感谢你能来特纳府邸
Thanks so much for coming in, chez Turner.
我穿成这样有点失礼了
Sorry for the...
西蒙 这是凯里警探
Simone, this is Detective Carey.
瑞秋
Rachel.
-你介意我 -没问题 请
- Do you mind if I...? - Yes, yes.
你不是不信任警察么
I thought you didn't trust the police.
信的
Yes.
我是说 我信任她
I mean, I trust her.
都没问题吧
All clear?
从现在开始
From now on,
要是你想联系我 就用这个
if you want to contact me, I'd like you to use this.
我能跟大臣单独聊几句吗
Would you mind if I had a word with the minister in private?
前大臣
Former...minister.
别掉队了
Keep up.
对 就是他
Yeah, it's him.
你确定吗
How confident are you?
很确定
I'm confident.
他们就是我看到的上了灰色面包车的人
Those are the guys I saw getting into the grey van.
能查出他们身份吗
Can you ID him?
戴着口罩呢 面部识别有难度
With that mask, facial rec won't be easy.
前提是 我还得找到个足够信任的人去查
That's if I can even find someone I trust enough to run
如果我把这个交给反恐指挥部
the search. If I give this to SO15,
他们会询问来源
they'll want to know where it came from.
你也不能说自己佩戴了隐藏摄像头
You can hardly say you were wearing a hidden camera.
我拍到了内政大臣承认
..I got the Home Secretary to admit
政府参与「移花接木」项目的视频
the government is complicit in Correction.
你用了卡迪加的领带相机
Khadija's tie camera? You did it?
说实话 我都不敢相信
Being honest, I've no idea
我都心如擂鼓了 怎么还能录下这一切
how I managed to record anything over the thumping of my heart!
我一直在想 他随时都会怀疑我
I kept thinking he'd suss me any second.
把这些拿给卡迪加够吗
Does that give us enough to take to Khadija?
抵制「移花接木」吗
Against Correction?  Mm.
我才摸着门道
I've barely got my foot in the door.
我得从内部见证英国的「移花接木」项目
I need to witness the UK Correction programme from the inside.
我得录下足够确凿的证据
I need to record enough evidence
来证明他们能做到什么地步
to prove what they're capable of, beyond doubt.
而且做这些的时候我还不能被抓住
And I need to do it all without getting caught.
所以你觉得需要多久
So, what are you thinking, potentially?
几个月
Months?
我不知道
I don't know.
-几年 -我不知道
- Years?  - I don't know.
牵涉其中的人
The people involved in this...
会不惜一切代价保守秘密
..they'll stop at nothing to keep it secret.
你看过新闻了吗
You've seen the latest?
拉各斯的事吗
The Lagos thing?
我不确定那是不是
Well, I wasn't sure if that was...
怎么 你觉得是真的是吗
What, you thought it was real?
你是政客
You're a politician.
-我不是那种政客 -我没有批判你的意思
- I'm not that kind of politician. - I wasn't judging.
都是计划中的一环
It's all part of it.
你自己也说
You said yourself,
并不是中国想控制我们的面部识别系统
this isn't China trying to take our facial rec.
有人想毁了我
Someone wants to destroy me.
你肯定树了不少劲故
You must have made some powerful enemies.
我想抓住杀害我朋友的人
I'm trying to catch the man who killed my friend.
要是能抓住他 也许他能把线索串起来
If we can get to him, maybe he can fill in the blanks.
我觉得我认识个能帮上忙的人
I think I know someone who can help.
我可不喜欢连我的私人预约 你手下都要跟踪
I don't appreciate your minion tailing me to a private appointment,
更别提还会跟你报告
much less reporting it.
我希望你清楚在做什么 把她纳入麾下
I hope you know what you're doing, taking her under your wing.
我谨代表机构 对凯里总督察的行为向你道歉
On behalf of the Service, I apologise for DCI Carey's behaviour.
-至于你的隐私 我 -胃
- As regards your privacy, I'm... - Stomach.
-他们觉得 -天啊
- They think... - Jesus...
弗兰克
..Frank.
让我像个害相思病的12岁小孩一样 守在电话旁边等
Got me waiting by the phone like a lovesick 12-year-old.
-你的医生是谁啊 -斯坦利·他妈的·库布里克
- Who's your doctor? - Stanley fucking Kubrick.
把摄像头塞我屁股里 我的喉咙里
Shoved a camera up my ass, down my throat.
现在他还想我吞下整个摄像头
Now he wants me to swallow one whole,
还嫌我被胃折腾的整晚睡不着不够难受
like my stomach hasn't been through enough fireball spinning all night long.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
大使馆那边呢 有在照顾你吗
What about the embassy? Are they looking after you?
我没跟他们说
I haven't told them.
一旦生病 他们瞅你眼神都不对了
You're sick, they look at you differently,
就像你不存在一样
like you're some sort of fucking nonentity.
我也保守过自己的秘密
I kept mine to myself.
你得过癌症
You had cancer?
跟同事说我去赫布里底群岛度假了
Told work I was glamping in the Hebrides.
其实 我是去皇家马斯登医院
In fact, I was having my thyroid gland removed at
切甲状腺去了
the Royal Marsden.
相对来说 我是幸运的
I was lucky, relatively.
没复发吗
It nerver came back?
不用化疗吗
No chemo?
七年没复发过
Complete remission for seven years.
恭喜
Mazel tov.
你觉得是因为什么
What do you put that down to?
抱歉 我约你来 不是病友交流病情的
Sorry, I didn't ask you here to swap health stories.
现在我都没法张口求你办事
And now I can't even ask you what I need to.
就因为我病了
Because I'm sick?
你刚才没听见我说什么吗
Didn't you just hear what I said?
BBC遭受了第二次黑客攻击
The BBC's suffered a second hack.
这次直接发生在《新闻之夜》演播室
This time direct on the Newsnight studio.
硬件设备也被黑了
The hardware sabotaged.
这算不上是问题
Still haven't heard a question.
我们调查了所有能接触到设备的人
We ran checks on everybody who had access to the equipment...
除了一个人
..with one exception.
你觉得是我派过去的那个孩子 是吗
You think it's the kid I sent, huh?
你觉得是路易破坏了你的新闻节目
You think Louie sabotaged your news programme?
真服了
I mean, Jesus Christ,
-我只是想帮你个忙 -我必须得问
- I was trying to do you a fucking favour.  - I had to ask.
幕后黑手完全有能力破坏先锋行动
Whoever's behind this has the capacity to compromise Operation Vanguard entirely.
北京干的
Beijing.
我们的怀疑方向正从中国调转开来
Our suspicions are shifting away from China.
调转到哪里去了呢
Ah, where are they shifting to?
我可以说
I could share that...
前提是你得愿意帮忙
..if you were prepared to help.
你指控我蓄意破坏 现在还想我帮你
You accuse me of sabotage, and now you want my help?
如果指控错了 那你就没理由不帮我了
If the accusation's false, you should have no reason not to.
嗯嗯嗯
Mm-mm-mm.
7楼已然沧陷 先锋行动需要个新家
The seventh floor is down. Vanguard needs a new home.
我就是那个用砖头盖房子的小猪
And I'm the little piggy who built his house out of brick.
你能让我们进去吗
Can you let us in?
考虑考虑
I'll consider it.
能尽快考虑吗
Can you consider it soon?
我们的警官已经被杀了
Our officers are being killed.
嗯 还真是抱歉了
Yeah, sorry about that.
弗林
Flynn.
真他妈可惜了
Fucking shame.
信仰
Faith.
什么意思
What's that?
我把康复归功于有信仰
What I put my recovery down to.
扯淡
Fuck off.
我算不上虔诚
Well, I was hardly devout.
我从主日学校退学了
I quit Sunday School
因为有人说我在圣经柜里亲莎拉·克劳利就是有罪
after they told me I'd sinned for kissing Sarah Crawley in the Bible cupboard.
但是 还挺管用
But, yeah, it helped.
重新审视我的宗教信仰
Revisiting my religion.
祈祷 忏悔 悔悟
Prayer, confession...repentance.
显然 我们的信仰不同
Obviously, we're not from the same faith.
我们背负着同样的重担
We carry the same burdens.
内疚和遗憾
Guilt and regret.
如果你想好起来
If you want to give yourself the best chance,
就得从这种情绪中解脱
you'll free yourself of them.
谁说我内疚和遗憾过了
Who says I have any guilt or regret?
一辈子干咱们这行
A lifetime in our trade?
得了吧 弗兰克
Come on, Frank.
别告诉我每晚让你夜不能寐的 只有你的胃
Don't tell me your stomach's the only thing keeping you awake at night.
-慢用 -谢谢
- Enjoy.  - Thank you.
特鲁罗数据分析公司
我只是来拿点东西
I just came to grab a few things.
马上就走 要去开会
I'm rushing straight out again. Due at a conference.
说实话 我宁愿完全避开这个地方
To tell you the truth, I'd rather avoid this place altogether.
一半客户都在同一栋大楼 想避开并不容易
Not easy when half your clients are in the same building.
能看得出你很忙
I can see how busy you are.
别这么说 他们说会有后续问话
Oh, no, please. They said there'd be follow-ups.
你同事今早来找过我
Your colleagues came to see me this morning.
案子有什么进展吗
Has there been a development in the case?
其实 诺克斯先生 我是来请你帮忙的
Actually, Mr Knox, I came to ask for your help.
帮忙
Help?
我知道你有权限使用
I understand you have access to
赞达科技面部识别软件
the Xanda Tech facial recognition software.
仅在中研委权限范围内使用
It-it-it was well within the CRC's remit
以评估赞达的能力
to assess Xanda's capabilities.
诺克斯先生 我不是来找你麻烦的 能给你看些东西吗
Mr Knox, you're not in trouble. May I show you something?
我明白了
I see.
口罩
The mask.
特纳说过赞达能识别口罩下的人脸
Turner said the Xanda programme can unmask?
是他吗
Is this him?
那个想杀我的人
The man who tried to kill me?
那个救你一命的警探 帕特里克·弗林
The detective who saved your life, Patrick Flynn...
他死了
..he died.
你帮我 我就能把凶手绳之以法
You help me, I can bring his killers to justice.
我会尽我所能
I'll do what I can.
外面人越来越多
It's getting busy out there.
真的 我真该去拉个选票
Really, I should start canvassing. Either that
或是跟邻居借支气步枪
or borrow an air rifle from one of the neighbours.
关于拉各斯 你还有什么
Is there anything else you want tell me...
要告诉我的吗
..about Lagos?
没 没有了
No, I don't think so.
我都不记得这事儿
I mean...I don't even remember that.
等下 这是我的手吗
Wait, is that supposed to be my hand?
哪只 端酒杯的那只
Which? The one holding the glass of wine,
还是楼她腰的那只
or the one holding her waist?
西蒙 这是假的
Simmy, this-this is faked.
假照片
Fake photo.
你就这理由
That's what you're going with.
也不都是假的 我是说 那不是我的手
Obviously not completely fake. But, I mean, that's not my hand.
不是你的手 那是谁的
Not your hand? Whose hand is it?
你知道我什么意思
Yeah, you know what I mean.
你看起来在葬礼上很是乐在其中嘛
You look like you were enjoying yourself at the funeral.
别这样
Come on.
那不是
I mean, that's not...
-当然不会一直哭哭啼啼的 -能看出来
- Obviously, it wasn't all doom and gloom.  - No, I can see!
当初你干嘛不带我一起去
Remind me why you didn't take me with you.
我干嘛不带你一起
Why I didn't take you with...?
是你自己不去 你不记得了吗
You're the one who chose not to come. Do you not remember?
哈里要上幼儿园 你也要回去上班
Harry was starting nursery. You were starting back at work.
你自己一人去 也没抱怨
You didn't complain, going alone.
再说了你跟我妈向也不大对付
Well, it's not exactly like the two of you saw eye-to-eye.
谁会跟自己婆婆相处融洽啊 可你还是去了
Who sees eye-to-eye with their mother-in-law? You still go.
那你也许是该去
Well, maybe you should have been there, then.
爸爸
Dad?
■
前大臣休假搞园艺
-谁拍的 -艾萨克 艾萨克
- Who took this?  - Isaac. Isaac!
露比 收拾行李 我们去姥姥家
Ruby, pack a bag, we're going to Nanny's.
喂
Oi! Oi!
他们给你多少钱
How much did they pay you for it?!
混蛋
Pricks!
谁住在那个房子里
Who lives in that house?
那边有绿色棚子的那间
The one over there with the green shed.
露比
Oh, uh, Rubes?
我让她收拾换洗衣服去了
I've told her to pack a change of clothes.
做什么
Why?
我带他们去我妈家
I'm taking them to Mum's.
不是吧 没必要这样
Oh, come on, please, you don't need to do that.
西蒙 你肯定能看出来这都是假的
Simmy, surely you can see this is all fake.
鲁比 带上牙刷
Ruby, and a toothbrush!
我得工作 孩子们不能一直待屋里
I need to work. The kids need to get out the house.
西蒙 我没楼她腰
Simm, I didn't put my hand on her waist.
证据确凿
It looked pretty convincing.
相信我 你不清楚这背后的阴谋
Trust me. You have no idea.
西蒙 好好想想
Simone, think about it.
要是你现在走了 别人会怎么看
If you leave now, how's it going to look?
你担心别人会怎么看
You're worried how it's going to look?
有点儿 这会让人觉得 我们家被私生子的言论影响到了
A bit, it makes it look like this love-child nonsense is getting to us.
就是影响到了 有点儿
It is. A bit!
起码让我送你们上车
OK, at least let me walk you to the car.
真希望你们为自己感到骄傲
I hope you're proud of yourselves.
您说什么 特纳先生
I beg your pardon, Mr Turner?
我说希望你们感到骄傲
I said I hope you're proud,
逼得我家人离开自己的家
forcing my family away from their home.
您同意做亲子鉴定吗 特纳先生
Will you agree to a paternity test, Mr Turner?
你巴不得呢 是吧
Ha-ha! You'd like that, wouldn't you?
-希望您能回答我们的问题 特纳先生 -我跟你说
- We'd like you to take our questions, Mr Turner.  - You know what?
如果你会如实报道 那我会回答的
I would take your questions if I could trust you to report my answers.
但你来这儿不是追寻真相的吧
But you're not here for the facts, are you?
你是来搅局的
You're here to stir the pot.
你来这儿 就是为了把这个无稽之谈变成丑闻
You're here to turn this nothing of a story into a scandal.
难怪主流媒体没救了 你没说错
No wonder mainstream media's time is up. You know what? You're right.
把你手机拿出来
Get your phones out.
要是你没跟主流媒体同流合污
If you're not part of the mainstream media,
就把手机拿出来 按下红色按钮
get your phones out and hit the red button,
因为你不可能指望这帮人说真话的
because you cannot trust this lot to tell the truth.
甚至都不怪他们 他们大部分人 所有人
It's not even their fault. Most of them, all of them,
根本不知道自己报道的新闻有多假
they don't have any idea how fake their own news is.
他们只管往前跑 追逐一个不存在的故事
They're just doing their jobs, chasing stories that don't exist,
不负责任地毁掉别人生活
ruining lives without taking responsibility.
我们见过多少次了 一家子人被这种
How many times have we seen families hounded by
无良媒体围攻 等真相大白
the media like this? Then the truth comes out
他们就拍拍屁股走人 他们道歉了吗
and they all move on, and do they apologise?
没有 当然没有 我跟你们说
No, of course not. You know what?
我有新闻给他们
I've got news for them.
真相即将揭晓
The truth IS coming.
等真相来临之时 你们都会知道的 相信我
And when it comes, you'll know about it, believe me.
会把这谎言打的落花流水
It's going to blow this bullshit right out of the water.
在那之前 我的建议是
Until then, my advice...?
他们说的话一个字儿都别信 借过
Don't believe a single word they tell you. Excuse me.
感谢您这么快就赶来 纳皮尔先生
Thank you for coming straight away, Mr Napier.
从您的CT中 我们可以看到
As we can see from your CT,
有明显的小曲胃壁增厚伴有大面积区域性腺病
there is significant lesser curve gastric wall thickening with extensive regional adenopathy.
还有大面积的病变
There appears to be extensive lesions within
位于肝脏右叶
the right lobe of the liver,
横隔膜上方有
and above the diaphragm there are
多个不到一厘米的
multiple sub-centimetre bilateral
-双侧肺部病变 -医生
- pulmonary lesions... - Doc.
过去四个月里 我的胃一直火烧火燎的
I've had a burning in the pit of my stomach for the past four months.
不管你想告诉我什么
Whatever you've got to tell me,
我都预想到了 而且还往更坏的方向想过
I've already imagined it and worse.
所以麻烦你说人话 我是什么情况
So, please, in English, what am I looking at?
胃癌四期
Stage four stomach cancer.
我们一收到您的活检结果
Once we've received the results of your biopsy,
就能做出诊断
we can make a diagnosis...
纳皮尔先生
Mr Napier,
一般来说 治疗过程中有朋友或家人
patients often find it useful to include a friend or a family member
的陪伴会相当有用
in this part of the process.
可以有人咨询问题 获取信息
Someone to ask questions, take information on board.
你能找到人陪你吗
Do you have somebody who could do that?
艾萨克·特纳今早在他家门口
Isaac Turner lashed out at the press on his doorstep this morning,
对英国媒体进行了猛烈抨击
in a tirade against the British media.
-你看了没 -家庭被无良媒体围攻
- You seen it?  - ...families hounded by the media like this!
他们道歉了吗 没有 当然没有
And do they apologise? No, of course not.
我跟你们说
You know what?
我有新闻给他们
I've got some news for them.
真相即将揭晓
The truth IS coming...
我去 他听起来像个宗教疯子
God, he sounds like a religious nut.
天啊
Jesus wept.
等真相来临之时 相信我
..and when it comes, believe me,
会把这谎言打的落花流水
it's going to blow this bullshit right out of the water.
在那之前 我的建议是
Until then, my advice?
他们说的话 一个字儿都别信
Don't believe a single word they tell you.
他的古怪行为源于
His erratic behaviour is the latest in
近期一系列丑闻
a long line of scandals...
你觉得我们尊敬的内政大臣会后悔
Do you think our esteemed Home Secretary regrets allowing
让艾萨克·特纳知道这么多内幕吗
Isaac Turner quite so much insight?
他又没挑明
It's not like he actually said it.
真的要等到挑明那天吗
Are we going to wait until he does?
你这样完全没有帮助
That was not helpful.
但把那帮媒体从我车道上赶走了 所以
It seems to have got the vultures off my drive, so...
"真相即将揭晓" 什么意思 预告吗
"The truth is coming"? What was that, a teaser?
"一个字儿都别信" 这句话更火一点
"Don't believe a single word" seems to be trending higher.
我告诉过你他们的能耐
I've told you what they're capable of.
你想昭告天下是吧
You want to scream from the rooftops?
会有机会的 但时机成熟前
You will get your chance. But until I tell you otherwise,
随他们说去
just...whatever they say,
低调行事 随它去
just keep your head down and go along with it.
诺克斯那边怎么样了
What about Knox?
他同意帮忙了吗
Did he agree to help?
费了番口舌
After some persuading.
我是过街老鼠 对吧
I'm toxic, right?
也许这个测试 能让大众对你有所改观
Maybe this test will buy you some favour.
测试
Test?
是啊 我看你推文了
Yeah. I saw your tweet.
#真实的萨克·特纳
"#TheRealZacTurner.
"期待亲子鉴定结果 没什么可隐瞒的"
"Looking forward to paternity test results. Nothing to hide."
搞什么
What the...?
这是我书房
That's my study.
看来不是你喽
I take it that's not you, then.
艾萨克
Isaac?
■
卡迪加·汗
我们得谈谈
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我只是想直接 冷静地回应
I just wanted to respond, directly and calmly,
你们听到的对于我的指控
to the allegations you're hearing about me,
我可以向你们保证 都是子虚乌有
which I can assure you are entirely without merit.
我没什么可隐瞒的
I've nothing to hide,
所以我会配合做亲子鉴定
which is why I am co-operating with the paternity test.
事实上 我已经同意
In fact, I have agreed
明早第一时间坐客BBC一频道
to appear first thing tomorrow morning on BBC One,
他们说到时侯会出结果
by which time, I'm told, we can expect a result,
来讲述我的故事
to give my side of the story.
所以 希望他们这次会听
So let's hope they listen.
期待早间时刻与各位见面
Looking forward to seeing you all at breakfast.
再说一遍 没什么可隐瞒的
Once again, nothing to hide.
这地方还真是随意啊
Well, this is random.
你指望什么 泰晤士河边长椅上相见吗
What were you expecting, a bench by the Thames?
这里监控拍不到 我又控制不了摄像头地点
It's a CCTV blind spot. I don't get to choose where they are.
你答应过给我独家的
You promised me an exclusive.
如果艾萨克·特纳情绪崩溃
If Isaac Turner has a meltdown
向所有拿手机的人脱口而出
and blurts it out to anyone with a phone,
-那就不叫独家 -他不会说的
- that's not exclusive. - He won't.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
你一点都不担心他脑子里在想什么吗
You're not just the least bit concerned about where his head's at?
欢迎来到这场「移花接木」的噩梦 艾萨克
Welcome to the nightmare that is Correction, Isaac.
这是罗文·吉尔吗
Is this Rowan Gill?
我们的敌人伪造了无法否认的事实
Our enemies fake things that we can't deny.
他用你的隐藏摄像头窃听了内政大臣
He bugged the Home Secretary with your hidden camera.
他脑子清醒得很
His head is in the right place.
最糟糕的是 不管我们承不承认 都完蛋了
Worst of all, if we do ever prove it or deny it, we're fucked.
-为什么 -你知道为什么 我们和他们一样有罪
Why?  - You know why. We're as guilty of it as they are!
我要这份文件
I'm going to need the file.
还不能给你
Not yet.
卡迪加 你知道冒进的风险
Khadija, you know the risks if we move too soon.
行吧 确保特纳别乱说话
Well, make sure Turner stays on point.
私生子的事儿我们给他压下来了
We sat on that love child story for him.
他却跑去斥责媒体来报答我们
He pays us back by ranting against the media?
他就是发泄一下
He was just letting off steam.
那套我也会
Well, two can play at that.
就是 拉比
You know, Rabbi...
想想你这辈子做的
..you think about all the good things
所有好事
that you did in your life and...
和所有坏事
And all the bad things?
我所做的一切
Everything I did...
每件事
..everything...
都是为了让这世界变得更安全
..was in the service of making the world a safer place.
我只是不确定
I'm just not sure that...
大家会不会也都这么认为
..everyone's going to see it that way.
所以这就是你时隔50年 再次回到犹太教堂的原因
So, this is why you've come back to shul after 50 years?
为了赎罪
To atone for your sins.
很抱歉让你失望了
Well, I'm sorry to disappoint you,
你来错地方了
but you've come to the wrong place.
再多的祷告也无法将你
No amount of prayers can save you
从对人类同胞的罪恶中拯救出来
from your sins against your fellow human beings,
没有拉比能宽恕你
and no rabbi can offer you forgiveness.
要如何赎罪 掌握在你手中
Your atonement is in your hands...
通过你的戒律
..through your mitzvahs...
你日常生活中的善行
..your good deeds in everyday life.
天啊 我给你打了一晚上电话
My God, I've been trying to call you all evening.
我刚哄孩子们睡觉去了
I was putting the kids to bed.
-再说了 我也知道你要说什么 -是么
- Besides, I know what you're going to say.  - Oh, yeah?
那条推文不是真的 都不是真的
That tweet wasn't real, nothing's real.
那在咱家门口吼人的事儿呢 是真的吗
What about that rant on our doorstep? Was that real?
是
Uh, yeah.
那是真的
That was real.
听着 西蒙
Listen, Simone...
明早 在电视上
..tomorrow morning, on the TV...
他们会让人觉得我就是那个男孩的父亲
..they're going to make it seem like I'm the father of that boy.
谁能恨你恨到对你做出这些事 艾萨克
Who hates you enough to do all this, Isaac?
除了现在的我
I mean, apart from me right now.
你为什么犹像
Why do you hesitate?
之前 我建议你做亲子鉴定 你犹豫了
Earlier, when I suggested you do the paternity test, you hesitated.
有吗
Did I?
又来了
There it is again.
我不知道 西蒙
I don't know, Simone.
也许我就是他爸呢
Maybe I am the father.
他跟你长得很像
He looks like you.
什么
What?
维多利亚·贝洛的儿子 阿曼迪
Victoria Bello's son, Amandi.
我一直在看他
I've been looking at him.
所以 你到底想表达什么
So, I mean, what, what are you trying to say exactly?
我俩看起来一样是么
We all look the same?
不是 艾萨克
No, Isaac,
我想说的是 他看起来像你
I'm saying he looks like you.
等一下
Just wait one second.
艾萨克 怎么了
Isaac, what is it?
又来了个该死的记者 稍等 我再打给你
There's another fucking journalist. Hold on, I'll call you back.
这都晚上11点了
It's 11 o'clock at night!
你他妈知道自己在干嘛吗
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
我很抱歉迟到了
Look, I'm sorry for the tardiness.
我是来接艾萨克·特纳先生的
I'm here to pick up a Mr Isaac Turner?
要干什么
For what?
我要送你去媒体城
You're going to Media City?
-什么 曼彻斯特那个 -在索尔福德
- What, Manchester?  - Uh, Salford.
我要上电视么
I'm going to be on the telly, am I?
我想是的 先生
Well, I believe so, sir, yeah.
所以 BBC的早间新闻在等我吗
So, what, BBC Breakfast are expecting me?
你是艾萨克·特纳吧
You are...Isaac Turner?
请坐后面 随意点 先生
Make yourself comfortable in the back, sir.
就一口 释放压力的
Just one puff. It'll stop you stressing all the time.
我会抽的
I'll smoke that...
如果你喝口这个 纯的
..if you drink this, neat.
谁还说"纯的"啊
Who says "neat"?
你的口气听起来就像爸爸
It sounds like something Dad would say.
意思是里面没掺东西 傻瓜
It means without a mixer, you idiot.
该你了
Your turn.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
那为什么
..firm but fair. So why, then,
这个声称跟安全大臣有私生子的女人
did the woman who claims to have had a lovechild with the Security Minster
护照申请受理时间
find her application languishing in
是平均时间的五倍呢
the system five times longer than average?
是巧合 还是故意干涉
Coincidence or interference?
我们与在拉各斯家中的
In an exclusive interview,
维多利亚·贝洛 进行了一次独家采访
we speak to Victoria Bello from her home in Lagos.
见鬼
Oh, fuck.
内政部一遍遍地告诉我
I was told over and over by the Home Office
找不到我的申请表
that my application could not be traced.
他们有次还说 一定是我搞错了
Once, they even told me that I must have been mistaken
一定是我没有申请
and I couldn't have applied,
似乎故意想消磨我的心力
as if they were trying to wear me down.
我对艾萨克·特纳先生别无所求
Look, I don't want anything from Mr Isaac Turner.
但我儿子有权在他父亲的国家长大
But my son has the right to grow up in the country of his father.
稍后 我会采访在野党内阁大臣
Later I'll be speaking to the Shadow Home Secretary,
关于内政部对贝洛绿卡申请不当处理一案
who is leading the calls for an urgent inquiry into
他带头呼吁展开紧急调查
the mishandling of Bello's case by the Home Office.
阿比 我想你说的对
You do? Oh, Abby, I think you're right.
我真的要睡觉了 跟你聊得很开心
I really do need to sleep. It's been really fun.
等等 我还没跟你讲我的播客呢
Wait, I still haven't told you about my podcast.
行吧 你说吧
Go on, then, tell me about your podcast.
-先别着急批评 朱迪法官 -嗯嗯
- Don't diss it till you've heard it, Judge Judy.  - Mm-hm.
你会很喜欢的
You'd actually be really into it.
我的节目有点像《连环杀手》 但名字叫《释放肖恩》
It's a bit like Serial, only it's called Free Shaun.
或许还可以起得更隐晦些 比如《公交站》
Or I might go more esoteric like The Bus Stop.
你在说啥
What are you talking about?
《释放肖恩》 是指肖恩·埃默里
Free Shaun? As in Shaun Emery?
一半的人认为 他杀了那个女人
Half the people think he killed that woman,
另一半则不这样想
the other half didn't.
但是他们不知道
But they don't know.
我其实见过他
I've met him.
阿比盖尔 肖恩·埃默里是有罪的
Abigail, Shaun Emery was guilty.
什么
What?
他在聆讯时认罪了 所以我很清楚 我也在场
He pleaded guilty at the hearing. I should know. I was there.
-可是你说 -我错了
- But you said...? - I was wrong.
听着 你做播客我觉得很好
Look, I-I think it's great that you're podcasting.
非常"纯"
I think it's really...neat.
但我觉得你该换个故事
But I just think you should pick a different story.
那个故事已经结束了
I mean, that story's over.
■
BBC晚间新闻揭开了
维多利亚·贝洛和她
儿子阿曼迪的故事
你会在唐列维酒店入住
They've got you staying at the Donlevy Hotel.
你想先登记入住 还是直接去演播室
Would you like to check in or go straight to the studio?
直接去演播室就行了
Yes, just go straight to the studio.
艾萨克
Isaac?
大... 哦 差点就叫你"大臣"了
Mini... Oops, nearly called you "Minister" then.
还不习惯 谢谢你来的这么早
Easily done. Thanks for coming in so horribly early.
这事发酵了这么久
After all the build-up,
我们只需要先聊聊私生子
we just had to lead with the lovechild.
所以 我真的要上电视了
So, I'm really going on, then?
我希望如此
Um, I certainly hope so!
我猜他们会黑进直播
I suppose they'll just hack into it live.
挺好奇他们这次想让我说什么
I wonder what they'll make me say this time.
你需要换下衣服吗
Do you, um, need somewhere to change?
不用
No.
行吧
Right, then.
休息室里有茶和咖啡
There's teas and coffees in the green room.
你也参与其中了吗
Are you a part of it?
参与什么其中
Part of...?
因为内部肯定有人接应
Cos someone must be, on the inside.
稍等
Just one second.
-喂 -艾萨克
- Hello?  - Isaac?
爱丽莎吗
Aliza?
还以为再也不用接你早6:00的电话了
I thought your 6am calls were a thing of the past.
除非是好消息 对吧
Only when it's good news, right?
怎么 你能证明没人干涉贝洛的申请吗
What, you can prove no-one's interfered with the Bello case?
不 那个我还没调查过
No. I haven't even looked into that.
行吧 《新闻之夜》已经在查了 所以好消息是什么
Right, well, Newsnight fucking have, so what's the good news?
你说得对 我一直在看你的支持率
You were right, of course. I have been checking the numbers.
从传统的平台上其实看不出来
You'd never know it from the usual platforms.
因为大家都对你恨意满满
The hate for you there is growing, if anything.
但在社交媒体的民意调查中
But across all social and polling...
你的支持率上来了
..your numbers are up.
不是那种陡然上升
I'm not talking about a spike,
但结合你发表种族定性评论 还有私生子的话题
but if you analyse the timeline from the racial profiling comments,
对媒体的谩骂 从时间线上综合来看
the lovechild allegations, the anti-media rant,
你的支持率在缓慢稳定上开
your approval is on a slow but steady uptick.
爱丽莎 有人想毁了我
Aliza, someone's trying to destroy me.
毁了你
Destroy you?
你的支持率可不答应
Tell your approval ratings that.
艾萨克
Isaac?
特纳先生 可以跟我来演播室吗
Mr Turner? Would you like to follow me to set?
艾萨克 和往常一样 先是整点新闻
Zac, just so you know, mate, it's the headlines on the hour as usual,
-然后我们会把话题引到你身上 -伦敦开始直播
- and then we're straight on to you. - London floor is live.
早上好 七国集团峰会定于
Good Morning. The G7 summit, due to take place...
-你是这周的话题人物 -索尔福德演播室 还有20秒
- You're having quite a week. - Salford studio, 20 seconds.
我们还在讨论措辞 到底是用车祸
We were debating whether to go with car crash,
一团糟 还是屎坑秀
dumpster fire or shitshow.
演播室直播 十 九
Studio live in ten, nine...
出错了 稍等
My mistake. Standing by.
突发新闻
And some breaking news.
尼日利亚护工维多利亚·贝洛的律师表示
Lawyers acting on behalf of Nigerian care worker Victoria Bello say
那份确定前安全大臣艾萨克·特纳
that a DNA test to determine whether former Security Minister Isaac Turner
是否是孩子生父的DNA检测
is the biological father of her child
结果为阴性
has produced a negative result.
艾萨克·特纳的传奇经历出现大转折
A surprising twist in the continued saga of Isaac Turner.
贝洛一家的代表律师
Lawyers working on behalf of the Bello family
表示计划进行第二次检测
say they plan to seek a second test.
我们稍后为您带来更多消息
We'll be back with more updates throughout the morning.
现在 镜头给曼彻斯特演播室的劳伦和威尔
Now, it's over to Lauren and Will in our Manchester studio.
大家早上好
Morning, all.  Good morning.
好吧 传奇故事还在继续
Well, the saga continues.
绝对延续到了这里
It certainly does here,
因为今天做客我们演播室的是
because first up on the sofa today is the man who is,
或者曾经是
or perhaps was,
所谓拉各斯私生子事件的核心人物
at the heart of the so-called Lagos lovechild allegations,
艾萨克·特纳 欢迎
Isaac Turner. Welcome.
早上好
Good Morning.
亲子鉴定结果呈阴性 你一定很高兴吧
Your paternity test has come back negative. You must be delighted.
不能说高兴
No, I'm not delighted.
我只是感谢这场闹剧终于结束了
I'm just... I'm glad this whole silly sideshow is over.
您从来没有否认过这些指控
I never actually heard you deny the claims.
大家都已经看到测试结果了
Well, you've seen the test results.
我有 我有听你否认
I have. I heard you deny them.
你之前发过视频 说自己没什么可隐瞒的
You uploaded a video, right, saying you had nothing to hide?
对 我觉得有必要让公众放心
Yeah. I-I felt it was important to reassure the public.
这就是你说的"真相即将揭开"吗
Is that what you meant by "The truth is coming?"
劳伦
You know, Lauren,
我和我的家人成为了一系列恶毒谎言的受害者
my family and I have been the target of some pretty nasty lies.
现在这些谎言终于被拆穿
Those lies have now been exposed,
我只希望大家都能回归正常生活
so, hopefully, everyone can go back to something like normal life.
你觉得她为什么要这么说呢
Why do you think she made those claims?
她肯定知道DNA测试会失败
She must have known the DNA test would fail.
我理解她的迫切心情
I understand the burning ambition
很多人都想来英国生活
people all over the world share to come here to the UK.
可惜 这意味着有些人为了插队
Unfortunately, it does mean that some people will go to desperate lengths
不惜铤而走险
to jump the queue.
正如我们的政府在宣言中所讲的那样
And, as the government said in its manifesto,
只有严格的移民制度 才能做到公平
our immigration system cannot be fair if it's not firm.
■
-
这人是谁？
他穿牛仔裤好有型！
我觉得那个拉各斯女人
就是为了傍大款...
如你所言
Mm. Well, as you brought up
政府宣言
manifesto promises,
而你已经不再是内政部一员
and as you're no longer at the Home Office,
政府已经作出决定了吗
has the government delivered on that one?
嗯 我认为首相
Well, I think the Prime Minister
正全力聚焦在
is laser-focused, rightly so...
在最紧迫的全球问题上
..on the most pressing global issues.
所以你是在怪内政大臣了 你的旧老板
So you blame the Home Secretary, then, your old boss?
你这是在揣测我的发言了
You're putting words into my mouth.
-你好 -警探 不确定你睡了没 我
- Hello.  - Detective? I wasn't sure if you'd be up. I'm....
我最近不太能睡得着
I'm not sleeping an awful lot at the moment.
对时间也没个概念
It's hard to tell what's early for other people.
-你说过一有消息 就打给你 -你说
- You did say to call as soon as I had something.  - Go on.
我对赞达的口罩下识别能力存疑
I was sceptical about Xanda's unmasking feature.
毕竟我们也在搞自己的模型
Given we're dealing with AI modelling,
我认为他们宣称的100%人脸识别准确率
I took their claims of 100% face-match accuracy
有夸大成分
with a sizeable pinch of salt.
但是呢
But...?
它确实匹配到了一张面孔
It's given us a face,
我又运行了一下搜索功能
and I've run the search function.
然后呢
And...?
当然 程序是无法访问犯罪数据库的
Well, naturally, the programme can't access the criminal databases you're
只能搜索到网上的东西
used to, it can only find what's online.
诺克斯先生 到底匹配到对象了吗
Mr Knox, do we have a match?
匹配到了
Yes.
看起来像是某个企业安全的网站
Looks like it's from some corporate security website.
尼古拉·米尔斯基
Nikolai Mirsky.
就这么多了
And that's about it.
姓名和国籍
His name and nationality.
-你怎么知道他的国籍的 -你看网页就知道了
- How do you know his nationality? - The web page it came from.
发过去了
Sending.
我没什么语言天赋 但是
Languages aren't my forte, but...
俄语长什么样我还是知道的
..I know what Russian looks like.
车马上就来
Car won't be a minute.
额 刚才怎么样
Oh, Erm... That... How did it go?
很好啊 我是说结果
Great.  I mean, the result,
-结果是阴性 这是真的吗 -是的
- it came back negative? That's what happened?  - Yeah.
也是这么播出去的 是吗
And that's what's going out, the same...?
我们给你办理了延时入住
They've booked you a late checkout.
回家之前先睡个好觉吧
Thought you might want to rest up before heading home.
可以去酒店休息下
The room's yours if you want it.
每个房间的迷你酒吧都是免费的
The mini bars in each room are fully complimentary.
全天候客房服务 平板电脑上有菜单
Room service is 24/7. You'll find the menus on the iPads,
可以通过门口电话让他们进来
and there's an entry phone by the door to buzz them in.
上网很简单 没密码 直接登录就可以了
Internet access is dead simple - no code, just log straight on.
好吧
All right.
很抱歉 我不
Oh. Uh, I'm so sorry. I don't...
别担心 没事
No worries. That's all right.
喂
Hello?
你好 艾萨克
Hello, Isaac.
你是谁
Who's this?
你知道我是谁
You know who it is.
你今天做得很好
You did good today.
这样下去的话 你都不需要我了
Carry on like that, you won't even need me.
听着 你们这些智能机器人
Listen, you AI robo fucks!
要是你能听到
If you're listening,
就离我和我家人远点
leave me and my family the fuck alone!
我知道你很生气
I understand you're upset.
别生气
But don't be.
我站在你这边
I'm on your side.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我只想谈谈
I just want to talk.
我们正在谈
We're talking.
不是在电话里谈
No, not like this.
面对面的
Face-to-face.
那你说怎么办
And how do you propose we do that?
喂
Hello?